Flesh? and sin die.
Die with Christ, that's it.
Rise with Christ.
That's it. Holy Spirit, come.
Holy Spirit come, set her free.
Die with Christ.
Holy Spirit, more.
Come with your Holy Spirit.
Fill me up.
Just words started coming.
Thank you, Lord!
What was I doing?
- What?
What you were doing?
You were praying in tongues.
Does it hurt?
- No.
Not at all?
In Jesus' name,
I thank you. Amen.
It's done!
Hallelujah!
...over one month
and she is in shock.
It's Jesus.
I used to watch
these things on TV
and sometimes I do not believe,
but today I do believe
because it happens to me.
Pain, go now.
And you can do this.
Now get all up.
It's good, yeah?
- Yeah.
Thank you Father. Amen.
Try to feel it.
Can you feel any difference?
Seriously, it does not hurt anymore.
Wow!
God, I thank you for healing. Thank you,
the pain is going to go.
Try to feel the head.
No!
I don't feel no pain, bro.
Now the pain is gone.
Now the pain is gone, yes.
We, as the church today, are standing
in front of a new reformation.
A reformation,
where we are coming back
to what we read
in the Book of Acts.
If you look at the church today,
it is so different from what we read
in the Book of Acts.
Because we have like
2000 years of history,
where the church has been changed
again and again.
We can see that the church
in the Book of Acts was a living body.
It was a body of believers
who were led by the Holy Spirit.
The church was a movement,
a disciples' movement.
Christianity moved to Greece
and became a philosophy.
It came to Italy and
became an institution.
It came to Europe and
became a culture.
It came to America and
became a business.
If you take a body and make
a business out of a body
is that not prostitution?
And this is what we have done
today with the church.
We have prostituted the church
of Christ, the body of Christ.
Because of that, we need
to see a reformation,